"use strict";function letsBegin(){welcome.classList.remove("active"),welcome.parentNode.removeChild(welcome),quizbox.classList.add("active"),document.getElementById("0").classList.add("active"),createBar(),progbar.classList.add("block")}function createBar(){progbar.style.width=barwidth+"%",progbar.style.transition="all 1s ease-in-out"}function updateBar(){var newwidth=barwidth+=percentage;progbar.style.width=newwidth+"%"}function checkAnswers(parentId,selectedAnswer){var parent=event.target.parentNode.parentNode;data[parentId].correctAnswer==selectedAnswer?(myScore+=1,parent.classList.add("correct")):parent.classList.add("wrong")}function displayResults(){var scoreContainer=document.createElement("div");scoreContainer.className="score__container";var resultsTextDiv=document.createElement("div");resultsTextDiv.className="results__text";var resultsText=document.createElement("h1");resultsText.innerHTML="Your Score is:";var resultsMessage=document.createElement("h3"),totalScore=document.createElement("div");totalScore.className="scorebox";var scoreText=document.createElement("h1"),fullScore=data.length,scoreTotal=document.createTextNode(myScore+"/"+fullScore),halfScore=fullScore/2;resultsMessage.innerHTML=myScore==fullScore?"Perfect score! Congratulations, you really know your stuff":halfScore<myScore?"Well done! Check below to see where you messed up":"Ouch! Someone needs to brush up on their trivia!",resultsTextDiv.appendChild(resultsText),scoreText.appendChild(scoreTotal),totalScore.appendChild(scoreText),scoreContainer.appendChild(resultsTextDiv),scoreContainer.appendChild(totalScore),scoreContainer.appendChild(resultsMessage),scoreContainer.appendChild(resetButton),resultsContainer.appendChild(scoreContainer);qList.parentNode;var qDivContainer=document.createElement("div");for(qDivContainer.className="questions__container",resultsContainer.appendChild(qDivContainer),i=0;i<data.length;i++){var qItem=q[i].children[0].innerHTML,qDiv=document.createElement("div"),qSpan=document.createElement("span"),qText=document.createTextNode(qItem);qSpan.appendChild(qText);var qTextDiv=document.createElement("div");qTextDiv.className="resultbox",qDiv.className="result__question";var answer=document.createElement("p"),incorrectnode=document.createTextNode("Correct answer: "+data[i].correctAnswer),incorrectP=document.createElement("p"),incorrectAnswer=document.createTextNode("Your Answer: "+yourAnswers[i].answer),correctnode=document.createTextNode("Your answer: "+data[i].correctAnswer);"question__box correct"===qList[i].className?(qDiv.classList.add("correct"),qTextDiv.appendChild(qSpan),answer.appendChild(correctnode)):(qDiv.classList.add("incorrect"),qTextDiv.appendChild(qSpan),incorrectP.appendChild(incorrectAnswer),answer.appendChild(incorrectnode),qTextDiv.appendChild(incorrectP)),qTextDiv.appendChild(answer),qDiv.appendChild(qTextDiv),qDivContainer.appendChild(qDiv)}"results active"==results.className&&(progbar.style.display="none",document.querySelector(".guess").style.overflow="scroll",document.querySelector(".guess").style.height="100%",document.querySelector(".game").style.height="100%"),resultsContainer.appendChild(qDivContainer)}function refresh(){window.location.reload()}var data=[{questionindex:0,question:"Which player scored the fastest hat-trick the Premier League history?",correctAnswer:"Sadio Mane",answers:["Cristiano Ronaldo","Sadio Mane","Harry Kane"]},{questionindex:1,question:"Which player has made the most Premier League appearances (653)?",correctAnswer:"Gareth Barry",answers:["Ryan Giggs","Frank Lampard","Gareth Barry"]},{questionindex:2,question:"Which former Tottenham manager has competed in the Dakar Rally?",correctAnswer:"Andre Villas-Boas",answers:["Andre Villas-Boas","Harry Redknapp","Martin Jol"]},{questionindex:3,question:"English rock star Elton John was twice the owner of which football club?",correctAnswer:"Watford",answers:["Wigan Athletic","Arsenal","Watford"]},{questionindex:4,question:"Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",correctAnswer:"Real Madrid",answers:["FC Barcelona","AC Milan","Real Madrid"]},{questionindex:5,question:"Which portuguese island is Cristiano Ronaldo from?",correctAnswer:"Madeira",answers:["Madeira","Santa Maria","Porto Santo"]},{questionindex:6,question:"How many clubs competed in the inaugural Premier League season?",correctAnswer:"22",answers:["22","20","19"]},{questionindex:7,question:"Who is Manchester Uniteds top premier league goal scorer?",correctAnswer:"Wayne Rooney",answers:["Sir Bobby Charlton","Wayne Rooney","David Beckham"]},{questionindex:8,question:"Which of the following player scored a hat-trick during their Manchester United debut?",correctAnswer:"Wayne Rooney",answers:["Cristiano Ronaldo","Robin Van Persie","Wayne Rooney"]},{questionindex:9,question:"From which club did Chelsea sign Didier Drogba?",correctAnswer:"Marseille",answers:["Juventus","Marseille","Ajax"]}],qActive=document.querySelector(".question__box.active"),activeQuestion={},yourAnswers=[],gamebox=document.getElementById("gameBox"),quizbox=document.getElementById("quiz"),welcome=(qActive=document.getElementsByClassName(".question__box.active"),document.querySelector(".welcome.active")),beginBtn=document.getElementById("begin"),welcomediv=document.getElementById("welcomeScreen"),progbar=document.getElementById("progBar"),percentage=100/data.length,barwidth=percentage;!function(){for(var i=0;i<data.length;i++){var quizitem=document.createElement("div");quizitem.className="question__box",quizitem.id=data[i].questionindex;var container=document.createElement("div");container.className="question__container";var qbox=document.createElement("div");qbox.className="question";var text=document.createElement("h2"),node=document.createTextNode(data[i].question),answers=data[i].answers,options=document.createElement("div");options.className="options";for(var a=0;a<answers.length;a++){document.createElement("div").className="option__box";var checkDiv=document.createElement("div");checkDiv.className="checkbox";var answerItem=document.createElement("input");answerItem.type="radio",answerItem.value=answers[a],answerItem.name="option";var label=document.createElement("label");label.htmlFor=answers[a],label.innerHTML=answers[a],checkDiv.appendChild(answerItem),checkDiv.appendChild(label),options.appendChild(checkDiv)}var submitAnswer=document.createElement("button");submitAnswer.className="submitbtn",(submitAnswer.onclick=submitAnswer).innerHTML="Submit";document.getElementById("questionNumber");var currentQ=document.createElement("div");currentQ.className="current__question";var currentQtext=document.createElement("h3"),newq=data[i].questionindex+1;currentQtext.innerHTML="Question: "+newq+"/"+data.length,text.appendChild(node),qbox.appendChild(text),currentQ.appendChild(currentQtext),container.appendChild(currentQ),container.appendChild(qbox),container.appendChild(options),container.appendChild(submitAnswer),quizitem.appendChild(container),quizbox.appendChild(quizitem)}}(),beginBtn.addEventListener("click",letsBegin);var results=document.getElementById("quizResults"),allbuttons=document.querySelectorAll(".submitbtn");!function(){var _iteratorNormalCompletion=!0,_didIteratorError=!1,_iteratorError=void 0;try{for(var _step,_iterator=allbuttons[Symbol.iterator]();!(_iteratorNormalCompletion=(_step=_iterator.next()).done);_iteratorNormalCompletion=!0){_step.value.addEventListener("click",function(event){var parent=event.target.parentNode.parentNode,parentId=parent.id,selected=parent.querySelector("input:checked"),nextQ=(parent.classList,parent.nextSibling);if(null!=selected){var selectedAnswer=selected.value;yourAnswers.push({answer:selectedAnswer}),selected||alert("Please select an answer!"),nextQ&&null!=selected&&(parent.classList.remove("active"),nextQ.className="question__box active",checkAnswers(parentId,selectedAnswer),updateBar()),nextQ||(checkAnswers(parentId,selectedAnswer),checkAnswers=function(){},quizbox.style.display="none",parent.classList.remove("active"),results.classList.add("active"),displayResults(),document.querySelector(".score__container").classList.add("active"),document.querySelector(".results__container").classList.add("active"))}else alert("Please select an answer")})}}catch(err){_didIteratorError=!0,_iteratorError=err}finally{try{!_iteratorNormalCompletion&&_iterator.return&&_iterator.return()}finally{if(_didIteratorError)throw _iteratorError}}}();var myScore=0,resultsContainer=document.getElementById("resultsContaier"),resetButton=document.createElement("button");resetButton.class="reset__button",resetButton.innerHTML="Play Again";var q=document.querySelectorAll(".question"),qList=document.querySelectorAll(".question__box");resetButton.addEventListener("click",refresh);